Joshua Churgin Full Stack Developer

054-339-2927 | joshuaschurgin@gmail.com | Github | Linkedin

Professional Summary

Ability to think outside the box brewery employee with .5 Year experience with Desire to create and Bring a good attitude to work. As someone who has just begun learning the field of coding, I am eager to improve my skills and get practice in the field. Well developed communication skills helped me work overseas in the tourism industry and agriculture industry.

Professional Skills

Front-end: HTML, CSS (including Bootstrap), JavaScript (ES6), React. Back-end: NodeJS, Express, SQL, MongoDB, Firebase, Heroku (Dyno).

Other relevant skills: REST APIs, Unit-Testing, Git.

Professional Experience

2021-2022 Brewery – staff member Beertzinut Craft Brewery Kibbutz Ketura

- Responsibility of bottling and labeling products for shipment.
- Maintenance and Handling of equipment for events and workshops.

2019-2021 Kibbutz Work Kibbutz Ketura Kibbutz Ketura

- Flexibility for position of work necessary for the community.
- Good with teamwork as most workplaces require it.

2018-2019 Winter Park Resort Winter Park Denver

- Attraction staff, safety supervision and customer engagement.
- Clearing out Equipment for maintenance of the attraction for the next day.

Education

2022 Fall: Full Stack Program; Israel Tech Challenge - TLV

A full-time training, hands-on accelerator that encourages research, autonomous learning, and teamwork, while putting an emphasis on the industry's best practices and needs.

2001-2013 Diploma, Maale Shacharut School, Eilot Regional council.

geography major - full bagrut.

Military Service

2013-2015, Volunteer in Special forces Equipment dev/manufacturer, 1 year in Egoz ,1 year in Rimon.

Additional Information

- Languages: Hebrew native, English native
- I like to play Soccer and American Football and in my free time some video games.